## CV of Stefan Brus, Software Developer!

- ""Simple things should be simple and complex things should be possible."
- Albert Einstein"
  - Michael Scott

Code: <a href="https://github.com/stefan-brus">https://github.com/stefan-brus</a>

Contact: stefan1brus [at] gmail (dot) com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-brus-95b27a161/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-brus-95b27a161/</a>



Me, circa 2018AD, state: baffled

#### **Hello World!**

I am a software developer with just about 10 years of professional experience. My main focus is on development and maintenance of performance-sensitive backend applications.

I consider myself to be language-agnostic, and have both personal and professional experience with a wide range of technologies.

Having worked almost exclusively in teams with other developers, I think of myself as a strong team player.

### **Professional Experience!**

# Software Engineer, Department of Computer Science, Linköping University, September 2009 - June 2010

- Implemented some features & created automated tests for the OpenModelica compiler
- Assisted with miscellaneous projects such as launching and maintaining websites

## Software Developer, Ida Infront AB, January 2011 - August 2013

- Main technologies used: Java, SQL databases
- Worked in client-facing teams, developing electronic archives and case management systems
- Additionally, designed some user-facing web forms and data analysis tools

# Software Developer, Sociomantic Labs GmbH, later dunnhumby Germany GmbH, September 2013 - November 2015

## Team Lead, Sociomantic Labs GmbH, later dunnhumby Germany GmbH, November 2015 - Present

- Main technologies used: The D language, SQL databases, Linux server clusters
- Started off as a backend software developer, and later took over as leader of one of the backend software teams
- Designed, implemented, and maintained real-time performance sensitive network applications
- Heavy focus on ensuring robustness and performance of microservice-based software systems, and single-threaded concurrency models



### **Education!**

### Computer Engineering, Linköping University, 2006 – 2009

- Focused on software engineering & programming
- Studied maths such as linear algebra, calculus, numerical analysis, statistics
- Learned about software design, operating systems, compilers, basic AI, software security

#### Skills!

### Languages

- D (experienced)
- Java (intermediate)
- Haskell (intermediate)
- C/C++ (intermediate)
- Python (basic)

### **Technologies**

- Linux command line
- Git version control
- SQL databases
- NoSQL such as redis, distributed hash tables
- Continuous integration (Jenkins)
- Containers (docker)
- Automation with scripts (shell)



Me, circa 2018AD, state: befuddled

